Guide to the Mark D. Weiser Papers, 1969-1999
Department of Special Collections
- Series 14. Media materials
  - Subseries B: CD-Roms
    - Association for Computing Machinery. Symposium on Principles of Programming Languages. POPL: the first ten years. Proceedings compendium, 1973-1983. c. 2, 1997, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 9)
    - Association for Computing Machinery. Symposium on Principles of Programming Languages. POPL: the first ten years. Proceedings compendium, 1973-1983, 1997, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 10)
    - Association for Computing Machinery. Special Interest Group on Operating Systems. Proceedings of the Fifteenth ACM Symposium on Operating Systems Principles. c. 2, 1995 Dec. 3-6, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 11)
    - Association for Computing Machinery. SIGGRAPH 98, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 12)
    - Apple Technology Group. Knowledge management technology review, 1997 Sept., 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 13)
    - Apple Technology Group. Knowledge management technology review. c. 2, 1997 Sept., 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 14)
    - BeOS. -- Release 3.1, n.d., 2 CD-Rom disk + 1 booklet (Box 131, Othertype 15)
    - Casio. The Casio LCD digital camera software QV-Link. -- Version 2.6, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 16)
    - Dataquest. How technology sells, n.d., 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 17)
    - Developer source, Vol. 4, 1996, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 18)
    - Developer source, Vol. 6, 1997, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 19)
    - FreebieSoft. Freebeez. -- Version 1.0, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 20)
    - Gartner Group. Symposium ITXPO98, Lake Buena Vista, Florida,, 1998 Oct. 12-16, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 21)
    - Gershenfeld, n.d., 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 22)
    - Hewlett Packard. HP Web PrintSmart, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 23)
    - IBM. ThinkPad customization CD for IBM ThinkPad 600, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 24)
    - IBM. Product recovery CD-ROM IBM ThinkPad [kit], 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk + 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. + 1 booklet (Box 131, Othertype 25)
    - Intel. Intel business video conferencing with ProShare Technology. -- Version 4.01, 1997, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 26)
    - Invention Machine. TechOptimizer. -- Professional ed., 1997, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 27)
    - Microsoft Developer Network. Development platform. -- Premium release, n.d., 4 CD-Rom disks (Box 131, Othertype 28)
    - Microsoft Developer Network. Libary - Visual studio 97. -- Special ed., 1997, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 29)
    - Microsoft Office 97. Developer edition tools, 1996, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 30)
    - Microsoft Office 97. -- Professional ed., 1996, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 1)
    - Microsoft Visual C++. -- Subscription. -- Version 4.0, 1995, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 2)
    - Microsoft Visual C++. -- Professional subscription. -- Version 4.1, 1996, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 3)
    - Microsoft Visual C++. -- Professional subscription. -- Version 4.2, 1996, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 4)
    - Microsoft Visual C++. -- Professional edition. -- Version 5, 1997, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 5)
    - Microsoft Visual Basic. -- Standard ed., 1995, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 6)
    - Microsoft Visual SourceSafe. -- Version 4.0, 1996, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 7)
    - Microsoft Windows98 for PCs without Windows, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 8)
    - Microsoft Office 2000 Beta 2, 1998, 11 CD-Rom disks (Box 132, Othertype 9)
    - Microsoft Windows NT Workstation operating system. -- Version 3.5, 1994, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 10)
    - Mitsui CD-R. Mind database, 1996 Feb. 16, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 11)
    - Nikon view. -- Version 1.0U, 1997, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 12)
    - NTP Software. Take control of NT: enhance and extend. Evaluation CD 7, n.d., 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 13)
    - OSDI '94 paper: Low power trace study, 1995, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 14)
    - REX TrueSync information manager, 1997, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 15)
    - Sierra CompleteHome. -- Version 2.0, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 16)
    - Sprite, 1984-1993, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 17)
    - Stanford Computer Forum. 1999 Student resumes, 1999, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 18)
    - Starfish. TrueSync desktop & TrueSync plus for REXpro, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 19)
    - Tanner EDA. Tanner tools, 1997, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 20)
    - Tanner EDA. Libraries. -- Version 6.0, 1997, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 21)
    - Telemedia Networks and Systems Group. The ViewStation software strikes back!, 1996, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 22)
    - University of Washington Dept. of Computer Science & Engineering. 1996-1997 undergraduate capstone design courses, 1997, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 23)
    - Xerox. The PARC story, 1996, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 24)
    - Xerox. XRCE: 10 years in Cambridge, 1988-1998, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 25)
    - SIGGRAPH 98: course notes, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 26)
    - SIGGRAPH 98: electronic art and animation catalog, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 27)
    - SIGGRAPH 98: proceedings, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 132, Othertype 28)
  - Subseries C: Audiocassettes
    - MicroSystems Forum. Tape 1, 1993 June 15-16, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 1)
    - MicroSystems Forum. Tape 2, 1993 June 15-16, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 2)
    - MicroSystems Forum. Tape 3, 1993 June 15-16, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 3)
    - MicroSystems Forum. Tape 4, 1993 June 15-16, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 4)
    - MicroSystems Forum. Tape 5, 1993 June 15-16, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 5)
    - MicroSystems Forum. Tape 6, 1993 June 15-16, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 6)
    - MicroSystems Forum. Tape 7, 1993 June 15-16, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 7)
    - MicroSystems Forum. Tape 8, 1993 June 15-16, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 8)
    - MicroSystems Forum. Tape 9, 1993 June 15-16, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 9)
    - MicroSystems Forum. Tape 10, 1993 June 15-16, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 10)
    - MicroSystems Forum. Tape 11, 1993 June 15-16, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 11)
    - Winter Technical Conference: Keynote address by Mark Weiser, 1995 January 16-20, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 12)
    - Xerox Mobile Professionals, 1995 October 10, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 13)
    - The Distinctiveness of Being Human Tape 1, n.d., 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 14)
    - The Distinctiveness of Being Human Tape 2, n.d., 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 15)
    - The Distinctiveness of Being Human Tape 3, n.d., 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 16)
    - 19th Global Electronic Document Systems Conference & Exhibit, 1998 November 8-13, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 17)
    - Beyond Computers: Radio Broadcast Show #5, n.d., 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 18)
    - To David from Mark, 1974 September 15, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 19)
    - Severe Tire Damage, 1994, 1 audiocassette (Box 133, Othertype 20)
  - Subseries D: Videotapes
    - Dealer, 1991 August 28, 1 video cassette: Super 8 (Box 133, Othertype 21)
    - Palainz dump, 1988 March 3, 1 video cassette: Super 8 (Box 133, Othertype 22)
    - Master Edited Tape for Text Editing, n.d., 1 video cassette: U-matic (Box 133, Othertype 23)
    - Mark Weiser, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 134, Othertype 1)
    - Sun GC Demo, 1988 September 23, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 134, Othertype 2)
    - Ubiquitous Computing, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 134, Othertype 3)
    - ORF Treffpunkt Kultur, 1997 August 9, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 134, Othertype 4)
    - ORF Treffpunkt Kultur, 1997 August 9, 1 video cassette: beta (Box 134, Othertype 5)
    - PBS: The Future is Now Part I:Business, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 134, Othertype 6)
    - Primetime, ABC: "Cutting Edge", 1997 October 17, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 134, Othertype 7)
    - World News Tonight, ABC: "Cutting Edge", 1997 October 15, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 134, Othertype 8)
    - CSL Visioning Interim Meeting, 1988 October 16, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 134, Othertype 9)
    - PARC Pad Case, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 134, Othertype 10)
    - Pie Menu, Job Windows Demo, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 135, Othertype 1)
    - STD@USENIX, 1997 January, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 135, Othertype 2)
    - Safety Tacit, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 135, Othertype 3)
    - Tacit Focus Group, 1995 July 25, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 135, Othertype 4)
    - Original Taping of Text Editing Instruction, July 21, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 135, Othertype 5)
    - Visiprog, n.d., 1 video cassette: BETA (Box 135, Othertype 6)
    - Visiprog, n.d., 1 video cassette: BETA (Box 135, Othertype 7)
    - Audra Weiser: Retirement, Mark Weiser Seminar, 1993 November 4, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 135, Othertype 8)
    - Paul Allaire XEN Broadcast "Direction '97 Deliver the Promise", 1997 January 29, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 135, Othertype 9)
    - Acoustic Ink Printing, Robert Sprague, 1997 January 23, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 135, Othertype 10)
    - The Corporate Innovation Council, 1997 February 27, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 136, Othertype 1)
    - Xerox 419 Docuquest, 1993 April 14, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 136, Othertype 2)
    - Forum: SemiConductor Technology Trends in the 21st Century, 1992 October 29, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 136, Othertype 3)
    - Forum: "Towards Conversational Computers", 1992 October 1, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 136, Othertype 4)
    - From Atoms to Cultures: A Visit to PARC, 1992 April 10, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 136, Othertype 5)
    - Information Visualizer for the Chrysler Innovation in Design Award, 1995 June, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 136, Othertype 6)
    - Innovations Excerpt: CSL Segment, 1992 June, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 136, Othertype 7)
    - Distinguished Lecture Series XIV: The New Internet Protocol, 1996 November 1, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 136, Othertype 8)
    - Information Visualizer for the Chrysler Innovation in Design Award, 1995 June, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 136, Othertype 9)
    - Leadership Through Technology, 1998 September 9, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 136, Othertype 10)
    - LiveBoard: A Solution for Interactive Collaboration, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 137, Othertype 1)
    - Modest Witness@Second Millenium, 1997 March 6, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 137, Othertype 2)
    - The Network Economy, 1996 December 12, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 137, Othertype 3)
    - PARC DocuWorld Presentation, 1998 August 18, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 137, Othertype 4)
    - PARC Follies, 1991 March 15, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 137, Othertype 5)
    - Personal Security Presentation, 1993 November 23, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 137, Othertype 6)
    - 3 R's: Reuse Reduce Recycle, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 137, Othertype 7)
    - Sexual Harassment Awareness, 1992 December 10, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 137, Othertype 8)
    - System 33, 1992 November, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 137, Othertype 9)
    - Tacit Focus Group #1, 1995 July 25, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 137, Othertype 10)
    - Workplace Scanning & Implications for Xerox, 1996 October, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 138, Othertype 1)
    - The Xerox LiveBoard, 1991 November 21, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 138, Othertype 2)
    - Xerox: Mobile Professionals, 1995 October 10, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 138, Othertype 3)
    - 24th Internat'l Conference: Computer Graphics & Interactive Techniques, 1997 August 5-7, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 138, Othertype 4)
    - Jeremy Cooperstock, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 138, Othertype 5)
    - Entrepreneurs, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 138, Othertype 6)
    - Evolution of Technology: The Reactive Room, 1995 February, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 138, Othertype 7)
    - CDI Promo #2, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 138, Othertype 8)
    - Excerpts from Saturday Night Live, 1993 October 23, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 138, Othertype 9)
    - The Future is Now, 1992 January 7, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 138, Othertype 10)
    - "High Stakes in Cyberspace", n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 139, Othertype 1)
    - IEEE Videoconference Series 1994 Tape 1, 1994 May 18, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 139, Othertype 2)
    - IEEE Videoconference Series 1994 Tape 2, 1994 May 18, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 139, Othertype 3)
    - Distinguished LEcture Series Vol III: James Donahue, 1989 November 29, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 139, Othertype 4)
    - Distinguished LEcture Series Vol III: Jim Gettys, 1991 February 11, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 139, Othertype 5)
    - Information at your Fingertips, 1990 November 12, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 139, Othertype 6)
    - The Information Exchange: Timex & Microsoft, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 139, Othertype 7)
    - Interactive Installations, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 139, Othertype 8)
    - Keeping the U.S. Computer and Communications Industry Competitive, 1995 June, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 139, Othertype 9)
    - LightLink Instant Communciation, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 139, Othertype 10)
    - Media Television Eps. 4-35, 1996 July 13, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 140, Othertype 1)
    - Minerva's Machine: Women and Computing, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 140, Othertype 2)
    - Nanotechnology, BBC, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 140, Othertype 3)
    - TechKnowledge, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 140, Othertype 4)
    - Open Up the Possibilities, 1995, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 140, Othertype 5)
    - Perspectives on the National Information Infrastructure, 1993 January 12, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 140, Othertype 6)
    - The Second Decade: Computer-Supported Collaboration, 1991 October 21, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 140, Othertype 7)
    - Sharpe's Eagle, 1995 June 18, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 140, Othertype 8)
    - Silicon Valley Story, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 140, Othertype 9)
    - Starfire: A Vision of Future Computing, 1995, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 140, Othertype 10)
    - The Student Electronic Notebook Project, 1991 April 23, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 141, Othertype 1)
    - Sunergy 25 "Next Generation Networking", 1997 March 6, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 141, Othertype 2)
    - Times Data Link Watch Dog to Vet Commercial, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 141, Othertype 3)
    - Towards 2000, 1992 December 8, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 141, Othertype 4)
    - Until We Sleep, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 141, Othertype 5)
    - UIST '97, 1997 October 14-17, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 141, Othertype 6)
    - UIST '98, 1998 November 1-4, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 141, Othertype 7)
    - CSIRO/Flinders Joint Research Centre: Annual Report, 1992 December, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 141, Othertype 8)
    - Visions of Heaven and Hell, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 141, Othertype 9)
    - WebBook and WebForager: An Information Workspace for the WWW, 1995 December 15, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 141, Othertype 10)
    - CS 547 Winograd, 1992 November 4, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 142, Othertype 1)
    - Women & the Future of Technology-Technology & the Future of Women, 1997 September 19, 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 142, Othertype 2)
    - Tape 2, n.d., 1 video cassette: beta (Box 142, Othertype 3)
    - Untitled, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 142, Othertype 4)
    - Untitled, n.d., 1 video cassette: VHS (Box 142, Othertype 5)
- Series 15. Academic files
  This series contains papers, class notes, course materials, and dissertation research materials created by Mark Weiser during his studies at the New College in Florida as well as at the University of Michigan.
  - High school and UNY at Stony Brook (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Philosophy 102, 1969 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous course readings (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - New College, 1970 - 1972 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - New College: educational contract (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - "New College: rich, radical, and hedonistic" Floridian, St. Petersburg Times, 1971 Nov. 14 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Heidegger and pragmatism: an overview plus conclusion / by Mark Weiser, n.d., tms (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Heidegger on being-with others / by Mark Weiser, n.d., tms (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Language, man, and truth / by Mark Weiser, 1971, tms (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Logical positivism (language and the world) / by Mark Weiser, [ca. 1971], tms (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Meaning, language-games, Wittgenstein, and What can be talked about: paper / by Mark Weiser, [ca. 1971], tms (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - [Memo] re: last Thursday's presentation for "Symbolism & experiences" to Douglas Berggren / Mark Weiser, 1971 May 15, tms (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Not freedom to, or freedom from! / Mark Weiser, n.d., ams (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Notes, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Notes on Being and time question, 1970 Dec. 1 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Paper on truth, n.d., draft (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Rational thought or "This could happen to you" / Mark Weiser, n.d., tms (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - Some ramblings relating to philosophy (reflections on Kant & others) / by Mark Weiser, 1971, tms (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Towards a theory of non-pejorative hierarchy / Mark Weiser, ca. 1974, ams (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - What is reality? 585 - 399 B.C. / by Mark Weiser, n.d., tms (Box 143, Folder 20)
  - Wittgenstein: the blue book and beyond / by Mark Weiser, n.d., tms (Box 143, Folder 21)
  - Graduate schools (Box 143, Folder 22)
  - University of Michigan graduate school (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - University of Michigan graduate school (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - University of Michigan graduate school (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - CCS 405 Prof. Zeigler, 1974 Fall (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - CCS 405: Modeling parallel process / Mark Weiser, 1974 Fall (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - CCS 500 Program inference by example. Riddle, 1976 Winter (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - CCS 500 Information theory & abstract computational complexity. Prof. Rollins, 1976 Winter (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - CCS 501 Computational complexity. Prof. Rounds, 1975 Fall (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - CCS 506. Prof. Conrad, 1976 Fall (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - CCS 510 class notes (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - CCS 510 labs (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - CCS 524 Speciation paper (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - CCS 524 Adaptive systems. Prof. Holland, 1976 Winter (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - CCS 525 Final paper: Can intelligence be artificial?, 1976 Jan. (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - CCS 580 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - CCS 640 Psychology (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - CCS 867. Prof. Meyers, 1975 Fall (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - CCS 867 bibliography [1 of 3], 1975 Fall (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - CCS 867 bibliography [2 of 3], 1975 Fall (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - CCS 867 bibliography [3 of 3], 1975 Fall (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - CICE 401 Linear algebra, 1975 Fall (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - CICE 512: Probability & stochastic processes: notes & exams, 1976 Winter (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - CICE 512 folder 2: homework assignments [1 of 2], 1976 Winter (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - CICE 512 folder 2: homework assignments [2 of 2], 1976 Winter (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Greek philosophy. Prof. Riley, 1971 Fall (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Human information processing CCS 525. Prof. Benson, 1975 Fall (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - MAT 565 Graph theory. Prof. Harary [1 of 2], 1975 Fall (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - MAT 565 Graph theory. Prof. Harary [2 of 2], 1975 Fall (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - MAT 582 Set theory. Prof. Hinman, 1973 Winter (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - MAT 684 Recursion-theoretic hierarchies. Prof. Hinman, 1972 Fall (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - MAT 684 Recursion-theoretic hierarchies. Prof. Hinman, 1973 Winter (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Philosophy 604 Philosophy of science seminar. Prof. Sklar, 1977 Winter (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - Philosophy 609 Philosophy of mind. Prof. Stich (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - 624, 1976 Fall (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - 630 notes (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - 630 notes [1 of 3] (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - 630 notes [2 of 3] (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - 630 notes [3 of 3] (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - More 630 notes (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - 805 Prof. Holland / Benson, 1977 Winter (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Applications of slices (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Abe Ellenberg slices (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Prospectus for dissertation (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Prospectus (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - Prospectus old (Box 147, Folder 12)
  - Proposed plan of study & research (Box 147, Folder 13)
  - Prelims (Box 147, Folder 14)
  - Quals (Box 147, Folder 15)
  - Typed in (Box 147, Folder 16)
  - Notes not typed in (Box 147, Folder 17)
  - Ideas file (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Summary report, 1977 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Paper on cell assemblies & models (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Thesis notes, 1979 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Prettifier LEVEL.SNO ALGOLW (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - ALGOLW & general systems (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - ALGOLW cartoons (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Visual mode - SDS (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Games policy (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Slices: POPL abstract (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Notes on slices chapter (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Experts and novices (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Slicing experiments pre-test results (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - Signed consent forms (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - Vita (Box 148, Folder 15)
  - Data analysis [1 of 3] (Box 148, Folder 16)
  - Data analysis [2 of 3] (Box 148, Folder 17)
  - Data analysis [3 of 3] (Box 148, Folder 18)
  - Score sheets (Box 148, Folder 19)
  - Road show (Box 148, Folder 20)
  - Cell assemblies (seminar) (Box 148, Folder 21)
  - Kaplan seminar (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Pilot study (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Slicing experiment test data (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Experimental design for slices (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Future experiments (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Program for slicing experiment (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Human Subjects Committee (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - St. Olaf College Fjelstad (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Munich Conference (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Slicing notes (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Absent members (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Notes on computing the exact schematic minimum (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Color dominance notes (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Early notes on slices [1 of 2] (Box 149, Folder 14)
  - Early notes on slices [2 of 2] (Box 149, Folder 15)
  - RSSM 69 (Box 149, Folder 16)
  - Color dominance (Box 149, Folder 17)
  - Slicer program (Box 149, Folder 18)
  - Theory I and II (Box 149, Folder 19)
  - Old thesis chapters (Box 149, Folder 20)
  - Evaluation of dissertation (Box 149, Folder 21)
  - P.M.F. [Program Management Facility] Design (Box 149, Folder 22)
  - Program Management Facility (Box 149, Folder 23)
  - Understanding programs (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - AAAS (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Modeling theory & program understanding (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Index cards (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Index cards (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Index cards (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Problem solving and raw score sheet with notes [1 of 2] (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Problem solving and raw score sheet with notes [2 of 2] (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Research subject questionnaire packets nos. 1-6 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Research subject questionnaire packets nos. 7-12 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - Research subject questionnaire packets nos. 13-15, 17, 19 + 2 unnumbered packets (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Dissertation research data, computer printouts (Box 151)
  - Dissertation research data, computer printouts (Box 152)
- Series 16. Teaching files